Doctor, I want to ask you an uncomfortable question. How many times this week did you ask a patient
의사 선생님, 불편할 수 있는 질문을 드리겠습니다. 이번 주에 환자에게 약물 알레르기가 있냐고 몇 번이나 물었습니까?
if they were allergic to any medication, and how many times had they already told you at a previous visit?
그리고 그 중 이전 방문 때 이미 말해 준 경우가 몇 번이었습니까?
This happens every day and it's not your fault — it's the system's fault. You chose dentistry to heal, to connect,
이것은 매일 일어납니다. 당신의 잘못이 아닙니다——시스템의 문제입니다. 치의학을 선택한 것은 치료하고, 연결하고,
to transform your patients' health, not to be the human form that asks the same questions over and over.
환자의 건강을 변화시키기 위해서입니다. 매번 같은 질문을 반복하는 인간 양식이 되기 위해서가 아닙니다.
Every appointment is costing you between 10 and 15 minutes just on repetitive questions.
매 진료마다 반복 질문만으로 10~15분이 소비되고 있습니다.
Multiply that by 20 appointments a week. That's up to 5 hours a week you don't get paid for,
주 20회 진료로 곱하면 급여도 안 되는 시간이 주 5시간이 됩니다.
don't rest during, and don't truly connect with your patient. And that's without counting the risk:
쉬지도 못하고, 환자와 진정한 연결도 없는 시간. 그뿐만이 아닙니다. 위험도 있습니다:
63% of your patients have hypertension, diabetes, or are taking anticoagulants.
환자의 63%는 고혈압, 당뇨병이 있거나 항응고제를 복용하고 있습니다.
If that information arrives late or incomplete, the mistake is yours.
그 정보가 늦거나 불완전하게 전달되면, 실수의 책임은 당신에게 있습니다.
Now imagine this: you arrive at your office at 8 a.m., you open Notion, and your first patient's clinical file is already ready.
이제 상상해보세요. 오전 8시에 진료실에 도착해 Notion을 열면 첫 번째 환자의 임상 기록이 이미 완성되어 있습니다.
Allergies, medications, risk factors, alerts — all processed by artificial intelligence, all waiting for you.
알레르기, 약물, 위험 요소, 알림—— 모두 인공지능으로 처리되어 당신을 기다리고 있습니다.
You walk in, you see them, they feel like you've known them their whole life.
진료실에 들어가 환자를 보면, 환자는 당신이 평생 알아온 것처럼 느낍니다.
This isn't the future. This is DentBot and it's already available. DentBot is an automation that connects a WhatsApp form with AI.
이것은 미래가 아닙니다. 이것이 DentBot이고, 이미 사용 가능합니다. DentBot은 WhatsApp 양식을 AI와 연결하는 자동화입니다.
It generates two clinical files before the appointment even starts. Here's how: the day before, the patient receives a link via WhatsApp.
진료가 시작되기 전에 두 개의 임상 기록을 생성합니다. 작동 방식: 전날 환자가 WhatsApp으로 링크를 받습니다.
They open it on their phone, no apps, no login, and in 3 minutes they fill out their medical history.
스마트폰에서 열고, 앱이나 로그인 없이, 3분 만에 병력을 작성합니다.
Once the form is submitted, the bot starts working, and that's where the magic happens.
양식을 제출하면 봇이 작동하기 시작하고, 그때 마법이 일어납니다.
The AI processes everything: extracts allergies, medications, risk factors, and creates two documents in Notion at the same time.
AI가 모든 것을 처리합니다: 알레르기, 약물, 위험 요소를 추출하고 Notion에 동시에 두 문서를 생성합니다.
One for you, with all the information you need to arrive prepared. And one for your patient:
하나는 당신을 위한 것: 준비된 상태로 오는 데 필요한 모든 정보. 다른 하나는 환자를 위한 것:
a hyper-personalized summary you hand them at the end of the visit — something no non-AI practice can give them.
진료 마지막에 전달하는 초개인화된 요약—— AI 없는 진료실에서는 줄 수 없는 것.
The result: a dentist who arrives prepared, a patient who feels heard, and an experience that brings them back.
결과: 준비된 치과의사, 들은 느낌을 받는 환자, 그리고 다시 오게 만드는 경험.
DentBot has two plans. The Self-Setup at $9.99: you configure it yourself with the included instructions.
DentBot에는 두 가지 플랜이 있습니다. Self-Setup $9.99: 포함된 안내서로 직접 설정합니다.
The Complete Setup at $33: I configure it with you live, tailored to your practice, with the clinical Copilot included free.
Complete Setup $33: 제가 라이브로 함께 설정해 드립니다. 진료실에 맞게 조정하고, 임상 Copilot이 무료로 포함됩니다.
For comparison: traditional dental software charges between $80 and $200 per month. With DentBot, it's one time. Forever.
비교하면: 기존 치과 소프트웨어는 월 $80~$200를 청구합니다. DentBot은 한 번. 영원히.
And if that weren't enough, when you get the complete plan, you receive the DentBot Copilot absolutely free.
그것으로도 부족하다면, 완전 플랜을 구매하면 DentBot Copilot을 무료로 받습니다.
The DentBot Copilot is an AI assistant trained on 27 real clinical dental documents:
DentBot Copilot은 27개의 실제 임상 치과 문서로 학습한 AI 어시스턴트입니다:
PubMed papers, protocols from universities in Florida, Peru, Mexico, and Spain — all in one place.
PubMed 논문, 플로리다, 페루, 멕시코, 스페인 대학의 프로토콜——모두 한 곳에.
You can ask: "What do I do with a patient on bisphosphonates who needs an extraction?" or "What's the safe INR threshold to proceed?"
"비스포스포네이트 복용 환자에게 발치가 필요할 때 어떻게 하나요?" 또는 "안전한 INR 기준은 무엇인가요?"라고 물을 수 있습니다.
All sources are attached, and you can also create resources directly from the Copilot.
모든 출처가 첨부되어 있으며, Copilot으로 리소스를 만들 수도 있습니다.
The best part: it gives you an immediate answer, no Googling, no improvising — only verified clinical knowledge.
가장 좋은 점: Google 검색 없이, 즉각적인 답변—— 검증된 임상 지식만.
I only have eight spots available at this price. When they're gone, the price goes up. The link is below.
이 가격에는 8자리만 있습니다. 자리가 차면 가격이 오릅니다. 링크는 아래에 있습니다.
Go in and choose your plan. In less than 24 hours, your practice already operates differently.
들어가서 플랜을 선택하세요. 24시간 내에, 당신의 진료실은 이미 다르게 운영됩니다.